字
字
字幕
字幕
字幕製
字幕製
字幕製作
字幕製作
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人
字幕製作 ★ 至宏上人
♫ Snowing and blowing up bushels of fun. ♫
♫ Snowing and blowing up bushels of fun. ♫
Leanne?
琳恩？
♫ Now the jingle hop has- ♫
♫ Now the jingle hop has- ♫
♫ jingle bell, jingle bell jingle bell rock. ♫
♫ jingle bell, jingle bell jingle bell rock. ♫
♫ Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time. ♫
♫ Jingle bells chime in jingle bell time. ♫
♫ Dancing and prancing in jingle bell square. ♫
♫ Dancing and prancing in jingle bell square. ♫
♫ In the frosty air. ♫
♫ In the frosty air. ♫
♫ What a bright time it's the right time. ♫
♫ What a bright time it's the right time. ♫
♫ To rock the night away. ♫
♫ To rock the night away. ♫
♫ Jingle bell time is a swell time. ♫
♫ Jingle bell time is a swell time. ♫
♫ To go glidin' in a one-horse sleigh ♫
♫ To go glidin' in a one-horse sleigh ♫
♫ Mix and a-mingle in the jinglin' feet. ♫
♫ Mix and a-mingle in the jinglin' feet. ♫
♫ That's the jingle bell rock ♫
♫ That's the jingle bell rock ♫
Oh, my God!
喔，天啊！
Listen carefully.
仔細聽好了
Your wife has been taken.
你的妻子在我們手上
At 4:30 P.M.,
下午四點半
you will go to the Vatashca Street parking garage.
到Vitasha停車場二樓
There, an level 2 you will find a very special car.
你會看到一輛很特別的車
You will know which one.
你知道我什麼意思
Steal it.
搶過來
There are cameras installed on the inside and outside of this vehicle.
車裏有錄影鏡頭
I'm watching every move you make.
我能看到你的一舉一動
Drive it to the tap of the city and I will contact you there.
開車到山頂，我會再跟你聯繫
It's been a long time since you've driven...
我知道因為那次意外你很久沒有開車了…
But you'll have to overcome your fear if you want to save her.
但你必須克服你的恐懼，如果你還想救你的妻子
Your wife is very beautiful.
你的妻子很漂亮
If you want her back, then you will follow my instructions precisely.
如果你想她回到你身邊，那就按照我的指令行動
If you contact the police, or if you get caught...
如果你打算報警，或者你被逮捕…
She will die.
你就再也看不到她了
You've done very well so far, Mr. magma.
到目前為止你做的很好，麥格納先生
During the course of this night,
今晚的過程中
you will be given several tasks.
您將獲得各項任務
If you fail at  any...
如果你失敗了…
You will never see your wife again.
你永遠不會再看到你的妻子
How do you like the car?
那輛車怎麼樣？
Do you like it?
喜歡嗎？
It's armored.
改進了裝甲
It was designed especially for you.
是特別為你設計的
Is she alive?
我妻子還活著嗎？
The police will be looking for you.
警察會一直追捕你
If they catch you,  ever...
如果你被逮捕…
The game's over. Is that clear?
遊戲就結束，明白嗎？
Brent?
布蘭特？
Why is this happening?
發生了什麼事？
Please, help me. I'm so scared.
求求你，救我，我怕極了
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait!
要去哪裡？要去哪裡？等等！
She's fine.
她沒事
For now.
至少現在沒事
She will remain that way as long as you follow my instructions.
只要你老老實實按我說的做
I'm watching you, always.
我會一直看著你的
Get rid of your phone.
把手機扔掉
What do you want?
你想要做什麼？
Where are we?
要帶我去哪裡？
No! Please, please, don't leave me here!
不！求求你，放我出去！
No!
不要！
Answer.
我在
Speed up.
加速
Faster.
再加速
Turn left.
左轉
Go through the intersection and turn hard left.
穿過十字路口一直往前
No, I can't do that. I'll dead end into the park.
不行，前面是個公園
Just do it.
按我說的做
It's Christmas.
今天是聖誕節
There's gotta be hundreds of people in there.
公園裏有很多人
I won't ask again.
我不是在徵求你的意見
Shit.
媽的
Came an!
閃開！
Get out of my way.
快閃開
Drive toward the market.
去市場
Smash into everything you can.
你完全可以撞死他們
I can't do this!
我不能！
You have no choice.
你別無選擇的
Jesus.
天啊！
Excellent. Now drive onto the skating rink.
很好，現在去溜冰場
There's tan many people!
哇靠！那裏人更多！
Now.
快去
Get out of the way!
都給我閃開！
Go straight to the stage where the man is speaking. Knock it down.
到舞台那裏，撞死那個演講的
-I'll kill him.     -Do it.
-撞死他  -快去
-Are you crazy?     -Now.
-你就是個神經病？  -快去
Now go down the stairs.
現在衝下樓梯
Ah, shit.
喔，我靠
Ah...
喔…
Mr. magma, are you there?
麥格納先生，還在嗎？
Confirm you're still receiving.
快回答
I can hear you.
我還沒死
Where's my wife?
我的妻子在哪？
Keep going. Now.
我們繼續  快！
Watch out, watch out!
小心，小心！
Oh, no, no!
不，不，不！
Jesus.
天啊
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Your first task is complete.
布蘭特·麥格納先生，你的第一個任務完成了
Am I done?
是麼？
We're just getting started, my boy.
我們才剛開始
We're just getting started.
來我們繼續
Turn right, now.
右轉
-The water truck.     -Yeah?
-前面有輛飲料車  -喔？
Smash into it!
撞過去！
Don't stop.
別停
Speed up.
加速
-Faster.     -The light's red down there.
-快！  -前面是紅燈！
Go through it.
闖過去
Jesus.
天啊
Wonderful, Mr. Brent magma.
太漂亮了，布蘭特·麥格納先生
Now turn right. Pull into the underground construction zone.
現在右轉，去地下停車場
Relax...
放輕鬆…
And you will await further instructions.
等待下一步指示
Get out.
滾出去
-Get out, now!     -All right.
-滾出去，快！  -好了
Do not get out of the car.
別下車
You heard me asshole, get out.
沒聽到嗎？滾出去！快！
Now.
快！
-Look, you got the wrong car. Walk away...     -Now!
-你上錯了車…  -快！
-I'm doing you a favor.     -Get out.
-我有一個建議  -快滾出去
-You don't wanna... walk away.     -Get out.
-滾出去！  -快！
-You don't wanna steal...     -Get out of the car!
-你最好別搶這輛車…  -快滾出去！
-Drive away.     -I can't! I got a kid in the car!
-快開車  -靠！你沒看到這有個女孩嗎！
-Get out! What'?     -Drive away now!
-滾出去！  -快開車！
-Drive.     -What do you want meta do with her?
-開車  -現在怎麼辦？！
Drive away! Take her with you! Do it. Drive!
把她帶上！快開車！快點！
All right, all right, all right!
好了，好了，好了！
Get off of me, asshole!
把你的手拿開，你個混蛋！
Do not ever point a gun at me, you hear me'?
不要再拿槍指著我！
Do not ever point a gun at anyone!
也不要指著任何人！
Unh! Don't ever touch me like that again. Do you know what I could have done to you?
你也不要再碰我！
The hell are you doing?
什麼情況？你他媽在幹什麼？
Strap yourself in.
繫好安全帶
-I'm not doing shit!     -Put on your seatbelt.
-我才不繫！  -繫好安全帶
-No!     -Strap yourself in.
-就不繫！  -繫好安全帶
-Where are you going?     -Dust strap yourself in!
-你要去哪裏？  -繫好安全帶！
Kill her.
殺了她
She has seen you and she has seen the vehicle.
她見過你，見過這輛車
I'm not gonna do it. I can't do that.
不行，我做不到
You either shoot her...
殺了她…
Or I'm going to shoot your wife.
或者我殺了你妻子
One.
1…
Two.
2…
What? What? No.
什麼？什麼？不
I can't do that!
我不能殺了她！
I'm not a killer.
我不是殺人犯！
It's the right choice. You'll need her.
明智的選擇，你還用得到她
You can keep the car.
你繼續在車裏呆著
Can I get out new?
我能下車嗎？
I'll let you off right up here.     -She is not to be set free.
-為什麼？你害怕了嗎？  -她不能走
-L... listen.     -She is not to be set free.
-聽…我說！  -她不能下車，明白嗎？
-Understood?     -It's understand.
-明白了嗎？  -明白
Oh, great.
非常好
Oh, my God.
天啊
What did you do?
你幹什麼？
Pull aver!
靠邊！
Oh! Shit!
我靠！
On, God.
天啊
-What the hell are you doing?     -Put on your seatbelt!
-你到底幹了什麼？  -繫好安全帶！
Shit.
我靠
Hey, hey! Do not touch that gun, all right?
嘿！嘿！別碰槍？好嗎？
-I need bath hands to drive this car!     -Let go of me, asshole!
-我要兩隻手才能開車！  -放開我，混蛋！
Do not touch that gun!
不要再碰那把槍！
I don't care. I hope we crash. Help me!
我才不管，你最好撞壞這輛車
This guy's trying to kill me!
救命！這個大叔要殺我！
What are you doing?
你在犯什麼神經？
Pull us over!
快讓車停下來！救命！
Get in! Get inside the car!
快回來！
-This guy's crazy! Help me!     -Get inside this car, all right?
-他想殺我！救命！  -快回來！好嗎？
You understand me? Stay in the car!
給我老老實實呆在車裏！
Pull aver.
靠邊
Please slaw dawn.
快減速
-Oh, we're gonna die.     -Shut up.
-我靠，我會死的  -閉嘴
Oh, my God.
天啊
Shit.
我靠！
No, no, no.
靠，靠，靠
You're the shittiest driver I've ever seen.
你是我見過的最爛的車手
Back off, back off. Jesus!
閃開，快閃開！
On, shit!
我靠！
Is he dead?
他死了嗎？
I hope not.
我希望沒有
Listen to me, all right.
聽我說，行嗎？
I have gotta get this car out of the city right now,
我現在必須要開車出城
or they're gonna murder my wife.
不然他們會殺了我妻子
-You understand me'?     -Sure.
-你明白了嗎？  -當然
Let me give you a ward to the wise.
聽我一句勸，你下次偷車的時候
Next time you wanna steal a car, try to make sure that no one is in it.
先看看裏面有沒有人
-It works better.     -I'm not stealing it, you asshole. This is my car.
-就不會碰到這樣的事了  -我不是偷車賊，這輛車是我的，傻逼
What'?
什麼？
You probably don't understand this...
你不知道，因為…
"Because you're a criminal."
你才是偷車賊
Things in this world belong to people before people like you take them.
這世上每個東西都有自己的主人，但總有人喜歡偷走它
This car, which was really great...
這輛裝著鏡頭、電池、天線…
Till you added all these cameras to drain the battery...
的車是我的…
Belongs to me. How'd you find the car'?
那你是怎麼找到這車的？
I got a call from a cap saying he saw my car parked in the garage where I found you.
警察打電話給我，說看到我的車停在一個車庫裏，於是我就找到了你
What makes you think it was a cap?
你怎麼知道他就是警察？
Because he said so, genius.
當然是他說的啊，天才
What kind of cap calls to tell you he's got your car...
哪個警察會告訴你的車在哪…
But he still leaves me inside of it?
卻不帶你一起去？
-It wasn't the police that called.     -Then who was it?
-他根本不是警察  -那他是誰？
I don't know.
我不知道
-When was it stolen?     -Whenever you stale it.
-車是什麼時候被偷了？  -你偷的你問我？
When was the last time you saw it?
最後一次看到這車是什麼時候？
Two days ago, I guess. Look, you're obviously very disturbed.
我記得應該是兩天前，你看起來很不對勁
Whatever trouble you're in, you deserve it.
無論你碰到任何麻煩都是你自己的事情，現在我們來作筆交易
Sc I'll cut you a deal. Pull aver and I'll let you walk away.
靠邊，乖乖滾下車，我就不會報警抓你
Or what, you shunt me?
不然呢？你要打死我？
Give me back my gun and I will.
把槍給我，我很願意效勞
What's a kid doing with a gun, huh?
什麼樣的小孩會像你這樣用槍？
Sc if some dipshit like you steps to me, I can take care of it.
所以如果再碰到你這樣的白癡，我會小心的
That worked out well for you, didn't it?
這對你來說很好，不是嗎？
Did you recognize the voice, huh, that voice?
你聽不聽得出這是誰的聲音？
-Your friend who wanted you to kill me'?     -He's not my friend, okay'?
-你的朋友要你殺了我？  -這不是我朋友
I'm not the kind of person you wanna be caught kidnapping.
我不是你以為的容易被綁架的人
Yeah?
喔？是麼？
You special, is that it?
你跟普通人不一樣，對嗎？
Just do me one favor, will you?
幫我一個忙可以嗎？
Shut the hell up.
閉上你的嘴
You shut up!
你才給我閉嘴！
What are you doing? Hey.
你在做什麼？
What the hell?
你在犯什麼神經？
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way. ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells jingle all the way. ♫
♫ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ Oh, what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ Dashing through the snow. ♫
♫ Dashing through the snow. ♫
♫ In a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ In a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♫ O'er the hills we go. ♫
♫ O'er the hills we go. ♫
♫ Laughing all the way ♫
♫ Laughing all the way ♫
I can't believe you threw my phone out the window.
真不敢相信你把我的手機扔了出去
-I have a lot of money, you know.     -Good for you.
-我有很多錢，你知道嗎？  -看得出來
As in, if you let me go, I can give you a lot of money.
如果你放我走，我可以給你很多錢
I don't want your money.
我不要錢
What do you want?
那你想要什麼？
I want you to stop talking.
我要你閉嘴
And I want my wife back.
我要救我老婆
-And he tank her?     -He did.
-他綁架了你妻子？  -對
Whatever you awe him, I can get however much it is to pay him off, no problem.
好吧，我不管你們誰欠誰的
We'll take care of it right now.
這都不管我的事情
You have to let me go and stop almost killing us.
我不想在這死的不明不白
I would love to let you out of this car. Unfortunately, I can't do that.
我也想放你出去，但是不行
Why the hell not?
為什麼？
Because he asked me not to and I am doing whatever he asks.
因為他要我帶著你，因為我必須按他說的做
Se, what? What are you supposed to do?
那你打算怎麼辦？
I don't know.
我不知道
Well, who is he?
他是誰？
-I don't know.     -What do you know?
-我不知道  -那你知道些什麼？
Not much.
不多
No, no, no!
不，不，不！
Get up!
起床！
-Shut up.     -Ow! Aah!
-閉嘴  -哇！啊！
Please. Please. Please, don't shunt me. Please, don't shunt me.
求求你，別這樣，求求你
Quiet.
閉嘴
Answer.
我在
It's time for your next task.
你的下一個任務的時間
What is it?
是什麼呢？
More police are coming.
警察追來了
You'll have four minutes to getaway.
你有4分鐘的時間逃脫
You'll follow my instructions exactly.
嚴格按照我的指示
Someone wants to say hello.
有人想跟你打個招呼
Please, please.
求求你，求求你
Leanne?
琳恩？
Please. Help.
求求你，救救我
The clock starts now.
現在開始計時
Damn it!
我靠！
I'm totally screwed.
完蛋了
Oh!
喔！
-Ram him.     -What are you doing?
-加速前衝  -你要幹什麼？
-Oh, my God.     -Keep going.
-天啊  -繼續開
You're an idiot. That's assault with a deadly weapon.
你這個白癡，他們
They could shunt at us now.
會殺了你的
-Speed up.     -Shit.
-加速  -靠
Turn right now.
右轉，就是現在
Remember,
不要忘了
if they catch you...
如果你被逮捕…
You'll be a widower.
你的妻子就不保了
-Turn left.     -Oh, shit.
-左轉  -我靠
-Force him off the road.     -Look out!
-把他撞開  -小心！
-This is not very subtle!     -What are you talking about?
-我簡直不能相信是真的！  -你在說什麼？
You're not making yourself very hard to find.
你以後最好不要讓我看到你
God, I promise I'll be good from new an. Please let me live.
上帝，我今後一定好好做人，快救救我吧
-You're really not helping, okay'?     -Turn right.
-你確定不能閉上嘴嗎？  -右轉
Great.
非常好
Turn right down the alley.
右轉進巷子！
Skip!
住手！
Holy shit.
我靠！
-Two minutes.     -We're gonna die, please stop!
-2分鐘  -我們會死的，快停下來！
I don't think you'll make it.
我不認為你能成功
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Take a deep breath, okay? And calm down.
深呼吸，放鬆點
Shit.
我靠
I wouldn't relax just yet.
如果我是你，我就沒這麼樂觀
-Shit.     -Not again.
-靠  -不要
-Did you think we were done?     -No, don't!
-你逃脫了嗎？  -不，不要！
Goa!
天啊！
You're running out of time.
你的時間不多了
Oh! Oh!
喔！喔！
Tick tock, tick tock.
滴答，滴答
You have less than a minute.
不到一分鐘了
-Turn into the park.     -No, not the park!
-進入公園  -別進去！
Here we go.
沒事的，我們進去
Your wife's time is running out.
時間已經快到了
Watch out! Unh!
小心！
Go through the intersection.
衝過路口
All right, hold an!
再堅持一下！
Not much time, Mr. magma.
沒有時間了，麥格納先生
Oh, no!
天啊！
-No, please don't! Don't!     -Yep, yep, yep, hold on!
-不！別這樣！  -堅持就快了！
Five...
5…
Four... Came an, came an, came an!
4…快，快，快啊！
Three...
3…
-...mo...     -Oh!
-2…  -喔！
One...
1…
Zero.
0！
Bravo, Mr. Magna. Well done.
布蘭特·麥格納先生，幹得好！
Bravo.
完美
Your wife lives...
你的妻子還活著…
For now.
現在
Well dune.
幹得好
Answer.
我在
"Brent Magna is both reckless and fearful."
『布倫特·麥格納是一個魯莽可怕的人』
"He is, in short..."
『是一個，嗯…』
"...a dangerous driver and should pursue another profession."
『一個危險的車手，應該盡早換一份工作』
Remember that review? It wasn't very flattering.
你還記得他嗎？惹人厭的傢伙
They're blind to your real talents...
他們無視你真正的才華
Which are perfectly suited to my needs.
但我非常看好你
Do I know you?
我認識你嗎？
I know you, Mr. magma...
我認識你，麥格納先生…
-and I believe in you.     -Listen.
-而且我願意相信你  -聽我說
I need to know when this is all gonna be aver, all right? I need...
你什麼時候才能放我老婆出來？我要…
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
Hey, what are you doing?
嘿，你打算幹什麼？
-I hate you.     -Yeah, I love you.
-我恨你  -是麼，我愛你
You realize I'll just have to buy another limited edition shelby super snake...
你知道嗎我要重新買一輛謝爾比超級蛇限量版…
Take another six months to re-time the earns, open up the intake and customize it.
再花六個月的時間來改裝
And then I'm gonna drive it aver your face.
然後我要開著它壓過你的臉
-You sure know a lot about cars for...     -A girl'?
-你很懂機械，雖然你是個…  -是個女孩？
Yeah.
對
Wow.
哇喔
I like fast cars and computers and bay things, haw butch.
我喜歡跑車、電腦、很Man的東西
It's the 21st century, you should join it.
現在是21世紀了，你應該考慮加入我們
-What are you doing?     -I'm documenting this shit.
-你在做什麼？  -我要錄證據
I'm not going to jail after we get arrested.
被捕後我才不要去坐牢
-Well, nobody's gonna get caught, okay'?     -That's right, I forgot.
-沒有人會被捕，好嗎？  -喔對，我差點忘了
We're just gonna die...
我們會直接掛掉…
"Because you're a dumb-ass who attacks the police with a damn car."
就因為你這個白癡，攻擊警察
New every cap in this entire country...
現在全國每一個警察都想抓到我們…
Is hoping to put a couple bullets in our heads. Goad plan.
在我們的頭上來兩槍
-We are alive.     -Barely.
-我們還活著  -勉強活著
Not much of a thinker are you?
你又不是個偉大的思想家？
Well, I didn't actually graduate from charm school like you...
你知道嗎，其實我還沒有畢業…
So maybe someday you can give me some tutoring or something.
所以你或許還能教我點什麼
This is what he did to my beautiful, beautiful paint jab.
看看他幹的好事，我帥氣的跑車
Just get in the car.
快回來坐好
This is all the crap that he drilled into my carbon fiber interior.
看看我的碳纖維車蓋
This is the dumb-ass who got me into this mess.
這就是那個白癡，讓我陷入了這個爛攤子
-Stop filming me, all right'?     -Wave hi to the judge.
-別錄了  -跟法官打個招呼吧
-Say hi to all your new friends in jail.     -Hey! Put that away! I'm trying... just stop it.
-向你的獄友問個好  -快關掉
What is...? You're like add or something. What are you fiddling with new?
你現在又在幹什麼？
-Stop doing that.     -Why'?
-老實點可以嗎？  -為什麼要聽你的？
Because this guy is watching us, okay?
因為這傢伙在看著我們
-I need you to stop...     -I know what I'm doing.
-我希望你能安靜一會…  -我知道我在幹什麼
-Dust listen to me for two seconds.      -I know what I'm doing.
-你能安靜的呆2秒聽我說嗎？  -我知道我在幹什麼
See, I went to school and I know things...
我在學校接受到過教育…
Which is why I don't have to steal stuff, like some people.
這就是為什麼我不必去偷東西，不像某些人
If you're so smart, you tell me what's going on with all these cameras, huh?
既然你這麼聰明，能不能告訴我這些相機是怎麼回事
They're all linked to a single feed.
所有相機都連接到同一個端口
It's not only encrypted, but it's piggybacking on a public server.
沒有加密，但是盜用了政府伺服器
Huh?
喔？
It means they're hosting this live feed from these cameras...
也就是說
An a government server without them knowing about it.
他們能直接使用政府伺服器
Sc anybody can watch it, even us.
可以看到城市裏所有角落
-Wait a second.     -What?
-等等  -怎麼了？
-These aren't coming from the same place.     -Where are they coming from?
-這些端口不來自同一個地方  -來自於哪裏？
Lacks like a parking garage.
看起來是個地下停車場
-Can you tell where it is?     -I don't know. Could be anywhere.
-你能獲取具體位置嗎？  -沒辦法，它可能在任何一個地方
-Do you think it's where he might be'?     -Doubt it. But he can see it.
-你覺得會在哪裏？  -我不確定
I don't like that he's watching us.
但他可以看到我們，讓我很不爽
Do you think you can track him with that thing?
您可以追蹤到他嗎？
No, and if anyone did, he would just dump the ip address.
不行，如果有人試圖追蹤，他就會改變IP地址
As long as his feed is hosted remotely, there's no way to find it.
只要他用的是伺服器，就有沒有辦法找到它
-And that thing isn't really well-hidden.     -What?
-但是有其他方法  -什麼？
Microphone.
麥克風
-Oh, so he's listening to us too'?     -Probably.
-你還在聽這個？  -或許吧
Well, I'll give you this, you are bright.
好我不得不承認，你很聰明
It's called being educated.
這就是所謂的禮貌
You should look into it when you're not committing crimes.
你應該嘗試停止繼續犯罪
Scratch that, you'll be in jail.
如果你繼續這樣，他們會把你送進監獄
All right, answer.
我在
Pull up power plant on the GPS.
看導航儀上的地圖
We're kind of busy right now.
我現在有點忙
Learn to multitask.
你要學會一心兩用
Or let your new little friend help you. Lack under the visor.
或者向你的小夥伴尋求幫助
Won't you do that?
你能把遮陽板放下來嗎？
I'm uploading a new set of directions.
我發送了一個新的路線圖
That's the city power plant.
發電廠
"At exactly 11:30."
晚上十一點半
You will be there.
我在那等你
Why are we going to the power plant?
為什麼我們要去發電廠？
Always so inquisitive.
既然你誠心誠意的發問了，我就告訴你
I like it.
因為我喜歡
Listen carefully,
現在聽我說
you're to break into the central roam.
我要你到控制室裏
Access the remote system...
進入遠程伺服器…
-and insert that drive.     -What will that do?
-把這個密匙插進去  -你要幹什麼？
You're a clever girl. I'm sure you'll figure it out.
你是個聰明的女孩，你一定明白的
He wants to cut the power off. Why do you want to cut the power?
他要切斷電源，你為什麼要切斷電源？
You have some time until 11:30.
還要過一會才到十一點半
I wouldn't spend it trying to figure out my motives.
如果我是你，我不會浪費時間來瞭解我的動機
He's a real asshole.
他是一個徹底的混蛋
So you don't know who that is?
你不知道他是誰
No.
對
-No idea?     -I gut ideas.
-也沒有任何頭緒？  -我有一些猜測
People I used to work with...
可能是以前和我一起工作的人…
But nobody I know could set up something like this.
但我知道沒有人會安排這些事情
So why you'?
為什麼他選擇你？
Because I can drive.
因為我是個優秀的車手
-That's debatable.     -No, I mean, I used to race.
-關於這點還有待商確  -我的意思是在賽車場上
Really?
真的假的？
Really.
真的
Professionally, like, real racing.
專業，真正的賽車
Don't think I ever saw you an TV.
我不記得我在電視上見過你
There was a couple weeks there where you might have.
是啊，你在那可能有幾個星期了
And?
什麼？
And what?
什麼什麼？
I washed out.
我退出了比賽
How come'?
怎麼個情況？
I don't know, I just did. Doesn't matter now.
我也不知道，反正就是退出了，現在說這個沒意義
That's a pretty shitty answer.
真是個完美的回答
I washed out because I believed everybody who told me haw great I was.
我退出因為有人誇我有多麼偉大
Turns out the only thing I was great at was wrecking expensive cars.
原來我唯一擅長的就是撞毀昂貴的賽車
Sc I fell off the pro circuit and I awed a bunch of money.
我不再比賽後，欠了很多錢
This is the only thing I was ever any good at...
賽車是我唯一擅長的事情…
So I took whatever job paid the most.
對此我傾注了很多心血
I did some things I'm not proud of.
我贏了很多比賽，但我並不感到光榮
But then I got out of it. And this...
然後我就走了，而這個…
Is why.
我的妻子
She's beautiful.
她很漂亮
-Is she from here?     -Yeah.
-她是我們這兒的人？  -對
She always wanted to came back, so we thought...
她一直想回來，我們認為這會是個好地方…
It'd be a good place to lay law and start aver.
慢慢重新開始生活
Then I came home from work today, the dour is busted open...
我今天下班回家，看到大門開著…
The place is a wreck, there's bland on the floor.
地板上有血跡
My cell phone rings and this voice tells me...
然後我接到電話，告訴我說…
if I ever wanna s...
如果我想…
If I ever wanna see her again...
如果我想再次見到我的妻子…
I gotta do this jab.
我就必須按他們說的做
And if I tell anyone, she'll be dead.
如果我告訴任何人這事，我妻子就死定了
Next thing I know, I'm driving around in your car.
然後我就開著你的車
You souped this thing up yourself?
你改裝了這輛車？
Yeah, it was a graduation present.
對，這是我的畢業禮物
Nice. Something tells me your dad's not a mechanic.
調試的很好，也看出你父親不是一個機械師
He's the ceo of one of the largest banks in town.
他是我們這裏最大銀行的CEO
We moved here about two years ago for him to take it over.
我們大約兩年前搬到這裏
I barely see him,
之後就很少看到他
but this car is the nicest gift he ever gave me.
但這輛車是他給我的最好的禮物
Well, I'm sorry about all the damage.
很抱歉把你車搞成這樣
You know, you could also apologize for taking me hostage.
你道歉我也不一定就要原諒你
You could apologize for putting a gun in my face.
你也可以一槍打爆我的頭
I will if you let me out.
如果你讓我出去的話我會的
There's only one thing I'm concerned about right now...
現在我只關心一件事…
And I'm gonna do whatever I have to to get her back.
我會不惜一切代價救我的妻子
Sc if he says you gotta stay in the car, you gotta stay in the car.
所以他說要你留在車上，你就得呆著
And where does that get you?
為什麼你就得聽他的
Why is this happening? What is he after?
為什麼發生這些事？他到底要幹什麼？
You clearly haven't thought this through.
你顯然沒有想過這些問題
What happens when this is done and he gets what he wants?
當這一切結束時會發生什麼事？
Why would he even give her back to you?
為什麼他會讓你妻子回來？
If I were him, I'd kill her and I'd probably kill you.
如果我是他，我會殺了你妻子
Shit.
我靠
What?
怎麼了？
I'd probably kill me tan.
可能也會殺了我
Lacks like they've already been here.
看起來他們已經來過這裏
If he was already here, why didn't he just take out the power himself?
如果他在這裏，為什麼不自己去切斷電源？
I don't know.
我不知道
Stop here.
停車
Why?
怎麼了？
Ever see what happens to a metal car...
你不知道嗎，金屬的車輛…
When it touches a transformer that powers the whale city?
靠近變壓器會被電流擊穿的
Dust wait here, I'll handle it.
在這等著，我來處理
What, alone?
等等，什麼？
Yeah, just be ready to go.
我要進去
You sure?
你確定嗎？
Turn the car around, that's what I should do.
我應該把車開出去
No, I should gain after her.
不對，我應該開進去
No, she's fine. She knows what she's doing.
不對，她很清醒，她知道她在做什麼
Hello? I don't have much time.
哈囉？聽得到嗎？我時間緊迫
I'm in this car with this man and his wife was kidnapped.
我與一名男子在車上，他的妻子被綁架
I speak English. Calm yourself.
請慢慢說英語
Could you just send someone, please?
快點派人來，快點！
-What is your, uh, emergency?     -I don't know.
-情況有多緊急？  -我不知道
It's this voice telling us what to do. You have to help us.
有人打電話命令我們按他說的做，你必須幫幫我們
-Exactly what is your location?     -I'm at the power plant.
-位置是在哪裏呢？  -我在發電廠
-You make it so much fun.     -Shit.
-哈哈哈，你很機靈  -媽的
Wherever that clever mind takes you, remember, I've already been there.
不管在哪裏都很聰明，我已經去過那裏了
Look around.
看看你的周圍
You see? That's right.
看到了嗎？就是那個
The police will think you blew up the power station.
警察會認為是你炸毀電廠的
Can I give you some advice?
我有個建議給你
Run.
快跑
Come on, come on.
快，快啊
-Go, go, go!     -What, what, what?
-走，走，快走！  -發生什麼事了？
-Drive, drive! Go!     -What happened?
-救命，救命啊！快走！  -發生什麼事了？
Hold on. Shit.
堅持一下，媽的
Aah!
啊！
Faster!
加速！
Go faster!
快加速！
Oh!
喔！
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你在做什麼？你在做什麼？
I'm not dying for you.
我不想因為你去坐牢！
-What happened?     -This is a part of his plan.
-發生了什麼事？  -這是他的計劃的一部分
I was an camera that whale time.
我剛才被監控拍下了
He could have taken out the power himself, but he lured us in there...
他玩弄我們在鼓掌之中…
"Because he wanted me to get caught an camera doing it."
他在一步步誘導我們
You think the caps would ever believe me new?
你以為警察現在還會相信我們嗎？
Before, it was just you...
開始這只是你自己的事情…
This car.
還把我的車拖下水
But new I'm screwed tan.
現在，我也被牽扯進來了
I'm sorry.
對不起
I gotta take care of myself.
我會照顧好我自己
Answer.
我在
Stop her from leaving.
不能讓她走
Go to hell.
見鬼去吧
Where are you taking me? Where are you taking me? Wait. Wait.
要去哪裡？要去哪裡？等等！
Leanne'? Leanne, can you hear me'?
琳恩！琳恩！你能聽到嗎？
Can you-f? Please.
聽到嗎？幫幫忙
Leanne, can you hear me?
琳恩，你能聽到我嗎？
Brent. Brent, what's going on?
布蘭特，這是怎麼回事？
Are you okay? Have they hurt you?
你還好嗎？他們傷害你了嗎？
-Why is this happening?     -Leanne.
-這是怎麼回事？  -琳恩！
-Please help me! Brent?     -Leanne, are you all right, baby?
-救救我！布蘭特  -琳恩！你受傷了，你還好嗎？
Please help me! I'm so scared.
快救救我！我好害怕
I'm coming after you. I'm gonna make all this better.
我馬上就來救你，一切都會結束的，好嗎？
-I'm gonna get...     -Aah!
-會結束的  -啊！
What...?
什麼…？
Put my wife back an! Put her back an!
放開我老婆！我要看到她！
Is my wife all right?
你們把我老婆怎麼樣了？
I told you not to let her out of the car.
我跟你說過不要讓她下車
-I just need to see if she's...     -I warned you.
-我只是想看看…  -我警告過你
I'm sorry.
對不起
It's not your fault.
這不是你的錯
I know what it's like to disappoint everyone, but I never thought that I'd let her dawn.
我知道我很沒用，但我不能放棄我老婆
She's still alive.
她還活著
You don't have to do this.
你沒有義務幫我
I want to.
我自願的
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
We gotta figure out his plan.
我猜到了他的計劃
On, shit.
我靠
Get dawn, get dawn. Came an.
躲下去，快
Okay, okay.
什麼都沒有
He was having you make this.
他讓你在路上製造混亂
You're blocking off a path.
警察封鎖了很多路口
Half of these are one-way streets.
這些路口一半以上都是單行道
With these intersections blacked off, no one will be able to get through here.
已經無法通行
Until they clean this mess up, there'll only be one way out of the city.
現在只有一條路可以出城
The rest will be a total shit show.
其他的都走不通
It's an escape route.
這看起來是一個撤退路線
I just wish I knew what he was after.
真想知道他到底要幹什麼
You and me bath.
我也是
-Answer.     -I have good news for you.
-我在  -有個好消息
This is your last assignment.
這是你最後一個任務了
Look up number five in the GPS.
查看你的導航
Follow the directions precisely. You have 10 minutes.
按照這個路線開，你有十分鐘
It's the bank.
銀行
What bank?
哪家銀行？
He wants us to rub my dad's bank.
他想讓我們搶我父親的銀行
Oh, shit.
我靠！
We can't do that.
我們不會去的
Do as instructed. The clock is ticking.
計時已經開始了
You can't. There's no way we could do that. The security's way tan tight.
我們兩個人怎麼可能搶的了銀行
Don't concern yourself with security.
不要在意這些細節
-He wants us to get caught.     -Follow the GPS. Turn around.
-他就是想要我們被抓住  -注意看導航，掉頭
This is a suicide mission. Listen, we can't do this.
這等於是自殺，我們不能去
Ignore her. Listen to me. Turn around now.
別理她，聽我指令，掉頭
Am I gonna see my wife again?
我要確定我妻子沒事
Turn around.
快掉頭
I'm losing my patience with you.
我耐心有限
Listen to me.
我們好好商量可以嗎？
No.
沒的商量
I need to know when I'm going to see my wife.
我什麼時候才能看到我老婆
No, turn the car around.
聽我的指令
This is your last warning.
我最後一次警告你
I need to be told that she is all right
我要看到她沒事
and when this shit is gonna be aver!
什麼時候才能結束這一切
Do you want to see her again?
你是不想再見到你妻子了嗎？
Get control of yourself and turn the car around.
把車開過去
You can't do this.
你別聽他的
-Listen to me, this is a setup.     -He will kill her.
-聽我說！這是一個陷阱！  -他們會殺了我老婆
That's why they used my car. It had to be me.
你知道為什麼他們要用我的車嗎？
Think about it.
仔細想想吧
My dad, he cut off all of my funds.
我爸斷了我的生活費
New my car is causing havoc all aver the city...
現在我的車在城裏亂竄
And I'm seen rubbing his bank?
然後所有人都看到我搶劫了銀行？
He wants us to get caught.
他就是想讓我當替罪羊
-What does he wanna steal?     -Money.
-他想要的是什麼？  -當然是錢
But that's just it, it's not that kind of bank.
這就是問題所在，它不是那種銀行
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
My dad runs an investment bank.
我爸爸那是一家投資銀行
-There's no cash.     -Oh, shit!
-根本沒有現金可以搶  -我靠！
-God.     -So, what, safety deposit boxes?
-天啊  -你是什麼意思，那只有保險櫃？
No, there's nothing like that in there, just computers.
也沒有保險櫃，那兒只有一堆電腦
-Bands. Bearer bands.     -Bearer bands? How old are you?
-債券呢？不記名債券  -債券？現在什麼年代了？
What is he after, then?
那他到底要幹嘛？
What's he trying to steal?
他要偷的是什麼？
Unless...
除非…
Hold an!
坐穩！
Unless what?
除非什麼？
Unless you don't want a record of your money.
除非你有一筆黑錢
-Right, right, like it's dirty money.     -Exactly.
-洗黑錢？  -沒錯
-How do you move dirty money?     -Look out, look out!
-怎麼才能洗乾淨黑錢呢？  -小心，小心！
-Came an, help me.     -They could encrypt the information...
-快說說  -銀行對賬戶數據進行加密的…
An a numeric transfer key. A flash drive with account numbers.
有一個數據傳輸密鑰
If you stale one of these little transfer keys, right...?
如果能拿到這個密鑰呢…？
-You could drain the accounts.     -Right.
-就可以使用那個賬戶  -對
No one would report that money stolen, it's not supposed to exist.
沒人會發現有錢被動過，賬戶根本就不存在
-Haw much are we talking about?     -It could be billions.
-會有多少錢？  -可能會有數十億美元
I should have been a banker.
我應該也去開個銀行
Tell me that you're not serious.
你不會真的要
Shit!
我靠！
-I'm gonna go for it.     -No, don't go for it!
-我會盡力的  -別，別這樣
Here we go!
嘿餵狗！
That was awesome.
我靠好險
Aah!
啊！
Aah! Get us out of here!
啊！滾開！
Watch out.
小心！
I really, really hate you.
我恨你一個洞
I can understand that.
我曉得
-What are you doing?     -Dust wait.
-你在做什麼？  -別廢話！
Okay, just sit still and be quiet for a minute.
好，我們保持冷靜，安靜的坐一會
Okay, it's dune. I bought us some time.
打完收工，我們贏得了一點時間
What?
什麼意思？
I hacked into the server connected to these cameras, put an a loop of us driving.
我進入伺服器，把剛才錄的一段視頻循環播放
-That's what he can see right now.     -Why?
-這樣他就暫時只能看到這個視頻  -幹嘛這樣？
Sc that you'll listen to me.
現在聽我說
When we get there, we're gonna get caught and your wife will die.
當我們到銀行後，我們會被抓住，他會殺了你妻子
We're his decays.
我們是他的誘餌
-Great.     -The powers out...
-非常好  -現在切斷了電源…
Which means the security infrastructure has been compromised.
銀行的安全系統就失效了
And when that happens, there's a procedure.
當發生這種情況，會啟動一個應急機制
Oh, shit.
我靠
My dad said something about this.
我父親曾經提到過這個的
They're being moved. They're moving them right now.
轉移，現在正在轉移
They move anything sensitive to a secure location until the system is back up...
把重要的數據轉移到一個安全的地方…
...and then they run a million tests.
…直到系統恢復正常
By the time we get there...
等我們到達銀行的時候…
We'll be rubbing an empty bank.
只有一個空蕩蕩的銀行
Please, let's just find a place to lack at it first.
現在我們要找個地方靜觀其變
I guarantee you it's swarming with caps.
我保證銀行周圍全都是警察
How long do we have?
我們有多少時間？
I don't know, five, maybe 10 minutes at the mast.
五到十分鐘
Watch where you're going, asshole!
看你能去哪裡，混蛋！
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
♫ With the kids jingle-balling. ♫
♫ With the kids jingle-balling. ♫
♫ And everyone telling you "be of good cheer". ♫
♫ And everyone telling you "be of good cheer". ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
♫ It's the most wonderful time of the year ♫
I'll go check it.
我去看看
Sc you were right?
怎麼樣了？
I wish I wasn't.
很糟糕
Se, what do we do new?
現在該怎麼辦？
I'm thinking.
我正在想
You said there was a procedure. If the power goes out,
你之前說如果電力中斷他們就會
they'll move the drives?
轉移數據？
Yeah.
對
Where do they move them?
轉去哪裏？
I don't know, it's classified information for the bank.
我不知道，這是銀行的機密
Right. Shit.
我靠
But they gotta get picked up. They have to be picked up from here.
但是他們要過去拿對不對，他們已經快得手了
They've got all these caps here waiting for us.
而所有警察都在這裏
I mean, what, is there a back door? Is there another entrance?
這兒有後門或其他入口嗎？
Remember that parking spat that we saw?
記得那個停車場嗎？
You asked if I thought that's where he was?
你覺得他會在那裏嗎？
Yeah.
有可能
Well, I bet he's there now.
我敢打賭，他就在那裏
I told you you were bright.
你可能是對的
Let's go.
我們走
Yeah.
接入碼
Three, one,
3，1…
nine, seven, two,
9，7，2…
one, three, four,
1，3，4…
two, six.
2，6…
What?
什麼？
Go, go, go!
快，快，快！
-You got it'?     -Yeah, go!
-好了  -走吧！
Get them!
快追上去！
Answer me.
接電話
Answer me, answer me.
接電話，接電話
Answer!
給我接電話！
Answer.
我在
You're dead. Your wife is dead. It's over! Don't play with me!
你死定了，你老婆完了，遊戲結束！
We hold the cards new, asshole!
現在我們佔上風，混蛋！
Could you be a little bit more careful?
你可以開穩一點嗎？
How do I get this drive out?
等我拔出密鑰？
Gut it!
到手了！
Knack him! Hit him!
撞他！撞他！
The voice speaks in german
你妹的！
Holy shit!
我靠！
Oh. My God, go!
天啊，快走！
-Get down, get down, get down!     -Do something!
趴下！趴下！
Please, get us out of here!
快離開這鬼地方
Oh!
喔！
Look out!
小心！
Hold on!
坐穩！
his is Sofia police department.
索非亞警方
Shit!
我靠
Pull aver the car now!
靠邊停車！
Lose them.
放棄抵抗
Driver, pull aver car now!
車裏的人，立刻靠邊停車
We're trapped. Sit back. Hold an. You ready?
我們被困住了，準備好了了嗎？
All right. Where's the gun? Where's the gun?
槍？槍呢？
-Give me the gun!     -Keep your hands where we can see them.
-把槍給我！  -你已經被包圍了
New, just go with me on this, all right? Just go with me.
好了跟我來，走
Back off!
別過來！
Or I will shunt her head! I will blow her brains out!
不然我打爆她的頭！
Back off! Hey! Hey! See this?
退後！沒看到嗎？
Back off, or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
退後，我會殺了她的
I will kill this girl right now
我會殺了她的
What the hell are you doing?
我要打爆她的頭！
I am going to blow her head off! Now, you. You. Yeah, you!
嘿！你！你！對就是你！
You okay? Hey!
你還好嗎？
Back, back, back! Or I'm killing this girl, you hear me?
都退後，我會殺了她的？
Back off! Back off!
退後！
That's it, you're doing great.
對很好，就這樣
Get out of my way, copper.
快閃開，條子們
I can't believe that worked.
真不敢相信這是我幹的
They're clear. I've sent you their location.
他們還沒被捕，我把位置給你
Intercept them.
抓住他們
What are you doing?
怎麼了？
I'm gonna let you out.
你快離開這
What?
什麼？
Came an. You're not a suspect anymore.
你不再有嫌疑
They think I kidnapped you. Tell them you were a hostage.
他們會認為你是被我綁架的
-No, I'm...     -I'm serious. I'm serious.
-不，我…  -我說真的
You've done more than enough for me.
你已經盡力了
I can't risk your life anymore.
我不能再讓你冒生命危險
-I really can't. You gotta get out, okay?     -No.
-你必須離開這  -不行
-Get out of the car.     -No.
-下車  -不
Came an, get out of the car, will you?
走吧，你快走吧
I'm coming with you.
我要跟你一起去
You're an extremely stubborn person, all right, you know that?
你真是個固執的人？
I know.
我知道
But I'm still not getting out of this car.
我不會離開我的車
Besides, without me, you'd probably do something stupid, like get your face shat off.
如果我不在你要打算怎麼辦
All right.
好吧
You don't even know my name, do you?
你還不知道我叫什麼名字吧？
No.
不知道
Aah! Go!
喔！快走！
Damn it!
我靠！
-Ow!     -Are you all right?
-哇！  -你沒事吧？
Hit him!
撞他！
Damn it!
趴下！
Dawn!
趴好！
Lack out!
小心！
Oh, God.
天啊
Get us off the train!
要掉下去了！
-Where's the gun? Find the gun!     -I don't know!
-槍在哪裏？  -我不知道！
-Find the gun!     -I'm lacking!
-槍在哪裏？  -我在找！
Find it!
快找槍！
-You got it'? Give it to me!     -I found it! Here!
-找到了嗎？快給我  -在這在這兒呢
Just hold the wheel for a second!
幫我扶一下方向盤！
I need you to downshift! You ready?
幫我掛到低檔，準備好了嗎？
Now!
快！
I have an idea.
我有一個想法
Get out.
下車
Sc we meet up with him.
我們去找他
We do an exchange. The drive for your wife.
我們用數據換你的妻子
It'll never work. He'll kill us.
他不會答應的，他會把我們都殺了
I have a way around it.
我有一個辦法
We use his camera to feed the video to the caps.
在車前架設鏡頭，把畫面發給警方
They'll see everything.
警察會明白一切
Answer the phone.
接電話
-Answer.     -You think you are so smart?
-我在  -你覺得你很
-I wouldn't be so...    -no, shut up and listen.
-聰明是不是…  -不，閉嘴
We have what you want, let's make a trade.
我們有你想要的，我要見你
Where?
在哪裏？
You know where I work?
在我上班的地方
I'll see you there in two hours.
給你兩小時到那
Goodnight, asshole.
晚安，混蛋
Where's my wife?
我老婆在哪？
Where's my drive?
我的密鑰呢？
No. No! No!
不，不！不！
Leanne!
琳恩！
Brent?
布蘭特？
I need to know they're real.
我要確定這是真的密鑰
You.
你
Fallow him.
跟著他！
Let her go first.
先放了他老婆
Oh, thank God you're here.
天啊，你終於來了
I love you.
我愛你
I'm waiting.
怎麼樣
Waiting.
稍等
Let's go.
我們該走了
Shoot them.
殺了他們！
Brent, look out!
布蘭特！小心！
No! No!
不！不！
-Throw her in!      -No! Aah!
-抓住她！  -不！啊！
-Are you all right?     -I'm okay.
-你還好嗎？  -我沒事
Shit, they gut the kid.
靠，他們抓走了那女孩
-I gotta go after her.     -Go get her.
-我要去救她  -快去
You stay with the police. Be careful.
你和警察呆在一起
Damn it!
你慢點！
Are you hurt, ma'am?
你受傷了嗎？
Shit.
靠
He has a gun an me.
他有槍
Brent, he has a gun.
快來救我
Please hear me.
聽見了沒
-I hope you can see this.     -sh
-你能看見這個平板嗎  -噓！
Quiet! Don't talk.
別說話
Brent, I'm trying to show you where we are.
布蘭特，我把位置發給你
Move out of my way!
別擋路！
Brent, yes!
布蘭特，你在哪！
-You're screwed, asshole!     -Shut up!
-你真他媽是混蛋！  -你閉嘴！
Come on, come on.
來吧，我們來玩吧
Oh!
啊！
Damn it!
我靠！
What are you doing? Is that a camera?
你在幹什麼？在錄影？
Give it to me, give it to me! No, give it back!
拿來！快給我！
Ah, shit! Bastard.
媽的！
Damn it!
我靠！
Shit.
靠
The only way out of the city.
這是唯一一條撤退的路
I know where she is.
我知道了
-Pull aver! Give me the gun!     -What are you doing? Stop it!
-把槍給我！  -你幹什麼，老實點！
You want us to die?
你死定了？
Brent'. Came an, came an!
布蘭特，快，快點！
-Get out!     -What?
-滾下車！  -什麼？
Now!
滾下車！
Are you okay?
沒事吧？
Are you okay? Yeah.
你還好嗎？
Stay there. You're under arrest.
你被捕了
Thanks.
謝謝
Everybody back!
全部後退！
Ugh!
嗚！
-I guess I owe you one, huh?     -And you owe me a new car.
-我欠你一個人情  是吧？  -你欠我一輛新車
Don't worry about the car. It just needs a new paint jab and she'll be fine.
別擔心，它只是需要一個修理工
-What's that?     -I don't know.
-什麼聲音？  -不知道
It's not mine.
不是我的手機
-Hello'?     -Aren't you going to thank me?
-喂  -不用謝我
I did for you what you could never do for yourself.
我幫你做到你做不到的事
I showed you what you are made of.
我看到了你的表現
Please  excuse me if I wasn't able to be there in person.
請原諒我
I'm sure you understand, under the circumstances...
不能親自到場
It would have been most inconvenient for me.
我有點不方便…
If you're asking yourself who I am to you...
你一定想知道他們是誰…
I am your greatest fan.
他們都是你狂熱的崇拜者
I always thought you could have been at the top of your profession...
我一直認為你可以在自己的領域獨領風騷…
If only you believed you could.
只要你相信自己
So that's it, you see.
你看，你做到了
Please send your lovely wife my best wishes for a happy Christmas.
請允許我對你的妻子致以最誠摯的祝福
I'm sincerely glad you worked things out to be with her for the holidays.
我很喜歡她為你準備的聖誕節禮物
It's the season to be together with loved ones, so pm told.
多點時間陪陪自己的家人
I have very few loved ones.
我沒有什麼親人
My consolation is I have a lot of money.
唯一能安慰我的就是我有很多錢
And now, quite a lot more of it, thanks to you.
而現在我看到了你，非常感謝
I doubt if our paths will cross again, but then, life is full of surprises.
我們以後還會有交集的
So let's just say au
所以，現在還是先說一句
revoir.
再見
Be assured,
我向你保證…
it's been most entertaining.
以後會更加有意思的